小孩
我被锁在门外了
我找不到钥匙
你不是有我在备用钥匙吗
你能来给我开个门吗
嗯我等你
小二你来了
好好好
我站好
你开门
我有听话
没喝多少
真的
我确定
你干嘛那么严肃啊
今晚的活动先是公司聚餐
然后转场去唱歌
我没去
嗯怎么说的
我说家里有小孩等着
我才不是故意不带钥匙的
这不是忙了一周
好不容易有个周末假期
想从今天晚上就和你一起吧
干嘛至尊你肉麻
我偶尔肉麻一下
应该也不过分吧
你怎么知道我想喝水
就知道你最了解我
对了
前阵子你一直很喜欢的那个音箱
我买回来了
喏你慢点急什么
小孩你会跳舞吗
我教你跳舞吧
起来with me with my heart
Could i trigger when no time breaking
笨蛋绚烂
搂我的腰
你还会干嘛
平时怎么不见你
♪ Know you on the lady ♪
♪ I'm trying to stone brea ♪
♪ Giving my name ♪
♪ My head ♪
♪ And no play was true ♪
你知道跳舞什么比较重要吧
看着舞伴的眼睛
小孩stuck in my head
♪ Can be so bad ♪
学的很快啊
看来今晚的教学应该结束了
♪ In the end of fli to swear ♪
♪ I could look here at night ♪
这么熟练的搂腰又是从哪里学来的
哈哈看来是我的小孩长大了都到take me
♪ Which i love ♪
若是你回答下
♪ Through the turkedon't bui ♪
♪ Get you out ♪
I know you want it that
♪ So sin city and no shame ♪
♪ I've seen it all before you're ready districts and shine ♪
♪ Don't wanna hear them back ♪
♪ Cause i still thinking about the time ♪
♪ I don't let my fingers on you ♪
♪ Who will live in a bulin crack breaking back ♪
♪ Got the flash ma ♪
♪ How could you bury sor step in that dress ♪
♪ Well ♪
♪ Leaking another spell like you ♪
♪ Sneak another si see rose ar you ♪
♪ Hear the rules are ♪